hostsearch.com 2008-12-18

# Web Hosting Search & Web Host Directory - HostSearch.com

|   
---  
 **100GB** Space/ **1000GB** Bandwidth Free Domain芳ree Setup   
---  
Solutions for every size business. **Free Consultation**  
All-inclusive, no hidden fees, 30-day guarantee!   
Join now & get 120% commission from **Referback!**  
250GB Web Space, 6TB Xfer, UNLIMITED domains!   
350GB Disk Space 3000GB Bandwidth   
1000GB Disk Space Unlim. Bandwidth & **6 Months Free!**  
 **100% Satisfaction** Or Your Money Back!   
24/7 Supp, **UNLIMITED** domains, 300G HD, 3,000G BW   
 **5GB** HDD, **75GB** bw,24/7 support, **$1** for the first month   
  
|   
---  
**HostSearch.com Privacy Policy**  
---  
This website, all images, and content contained within is owned and operated by:  
  
Clicksee Network Co., Ltd.   
7th Floor, The Offices at Centralworld  
Rama 1 Road, Patumwan,  
Bangkok 10330   
Thailand 

We can be reached via email at support@hostsearch.com, or you can reach us by telephone at: +66-2-646 1818-21 , Fax: +66-2-646 1822 **Privacy Policy for Users of HostSearch.com**   
At HostSearch.com we are committed to protecting our users' right to privacy, and do not collect domain names or email addresses of our users for distribution or sale to advertisers. We adhere to a strict anti-spam policy, and at no time disclose user information to our advertisers. **Hyperlinks**   
HostSearch.com contains hyperlinks to other web sites, and this privacy policy applies only to material found in this site. **Security**   
We place a high importance on ensuring that transactions are secure. For this reason we take security precautions to protect against loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. As you may be aware, no data transmission over the Internet can be entirely secure. As a result, while we will always use reasonable endeavors to protect the personal information you provide to us, we cannot guarantee the security of your information and the use of our facilities (e.g. email) is at your own risk. **Termination**   
If either HostSearch or you wish to terminate the agreement between us this can be done by sending an email (by us to your e-mail address and by you to support@hostsearch.com or by post (by us to your usual address and by you to our registered office as given above). Notices will be deemed to have been served one hour after transmission by email and 3 working days after dispatch by post. You are responsible for notifying HostSearch of any change to your email address and, when provided, your postal address. Any breach of these terms shall entitle HostSearch to immediately terminate the service to you without notice. Neither party is obliged to provide to the other any reason for their decision to terminate the agreement.
